(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-13T03:16:19.055661",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Queen Mother Theater.
May I remind you to unwrap the snacks you may wish to nom,
and please switch your mobile phones on, as photography is allowed.
Please feel free to take screenshots during the performance using the hashtag #ERB3D.
Spread your Queen's performance far and wide.
本日はクイーン・マザー・シアターへご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to the Queen Mother Theater today.
開演に先立ち、いくつかご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, we have a few announcements.
館内での飲食は大歓迎です。
Eating and drinking inside the theater is highly welcomed.
お手元のお菓子はどうぞご自由にお楽しみください。
Please feel free to enjoy the snacks you have on hand.
本公演は撮影OK。
Photography is allowed during this performance.
携帯電話は電源オンのままで、
Please keep your mobile phones turned on.
スクリーンショットには「ERB3D」のハッシュタグを添え、
When sharing screenshots, please use the hashtag #ERB3D...
ぜひSNSへご投稿して、
...and feel free to post them on social media...
女王陛下の魅力を世界の隅々までお届けください。
...to spread the charm of Her Majesty to every corner of the world.
Thank you,
and enjoy the performance.
Huzzah!
さあ、それでは間もなく開演のお時間です。
Now then, it is almost time for the performance to begin.
どうぞお席にて、女王陛下の舞台を心行くまでお楽しみください。
Please take your seats and enjoy Her Majesty's stage to your heart's content.
ハッツァー！
Huzzah!
はっ！たぁ！
Hah! Take that!
おい、ついてこい！
Hey, keep up!
何よ、これ？！ そこをどきなさい！
What the frig?! Get out of my way!
あんたたちなんかと遊んでる暇はないの！
I don't have time to deal with the likes of you!
ちょっと、下がりなさい！ これでも喰らいなさい！
Wait, get back! And take this!
ふぅ、ダーリン...
Phew... Darling...
おーほっほっほ！ 身の程を知りなさい！
Ahahaha! Know your place!
私はエリザベス ローズ ブラッドフレイム！
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
この私に逆らう者に 慈悲など与えないわ！
And those who dare interfere with me... shall receive no mercy!
まったく、やれやれね。
Good grief.
よりによって今日、 私の3Dお披露目会なのに！
And today of all days... my commemorative 3D showcase!
こんなところで待ち伏せされるなんて、 厄介極まりないわ。
Getting ambushed like this... has been quite troublesome.
お披露目の準備や 練習が山積みだというのに、なんという不運！
Sod's law, with all the showcase preparations and practice I need to do!
こんなことに 時間を割いている余裕はないのよ。
I can't afford to waste time... on something like this.
一日が24時間じゃ足りないわ！ 本当にイライラする！
There's not enough hours in the day! How annoying!
よし、ソーン、そこにいなさい。 動いちゃダメよ。
All right, you pop yourself there, Thorn. Stay there, stay there.
聞いてちょうだい、私の自己紹介！
Listen to this... my self-introduction!
練習するわよ。こほん。
I shall practice. Ahem...
おーほっほっほ！
Ahahahaha!
薔薇は赤、我が心の炎は青、
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
スカーレット・クイーン、秩序の先触れ、 正義の導き手とも呼ばれる、
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of justice,
この私こそがエリザベス ローズ ブラッドフレイムよ！
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
お会いできて光栄だわ、本当に光栄よ！
Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
さて、どうかしら？
All right, well... How was that?
ノリが悪いわね。
Tough crowd.
大変！すごく遅れてるわ！ カラオケに行かなくちゃ、ソーン！早く行くわよ！
Oh gosh! I'm so behind! We need to get to the karaoke place, Thorn! Come on, let's go!
きゃっ！
Whoa!
冗談でしょ？！ またあんたたち？！
What the frig?! You lot again?!
本当に懲りない奴らね。
You never learn, do you?
よし、第二ラウンド開始よ！
All right, I guess it's time for round two!
これでも喰らえ！あぁもう、やられた...
Take that! Oh my god, I'm down...
よくも...
You dare...
我が炎を傷つけたわね？ 痛い目を見せてあげる！
...wound my flames? You'll pay for this!
いいでしょう。相手をしてあげるわ...
Very well. I'll deal with you...
3Dお披露目で歌う 曲の練習をしながらね！
...while practicing a song for my 3D showcase!
一石二鳥よ！
Two birds, one stone!
よく聴きなさい！ハッザー！
Listen well! Huzzah!
半端なら K.O.
If you do it half-heartedly, it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel lightheaded, go ahead.
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready to start the show?
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Whether you cry or laugh, love me still.
ほら Say No
Now, say "No"
低音 響かせろ
Make the bass reverberate
踊 踊 踊
Dance, dance, dance
なんとなくつまんない
Getting stuck with nothing but...
ことばっかで手詰まりでしょう保存
...somewhat boring things, aren't you?
論理 脳裏 膿の針 音楽を
Logic, in your mind, the festering needle—music is...
嫌になっちゃってドロドロに 爆破だわドロドロ
...getting sick of it, turning muddy, exploding like mud.
溺れて堕ちて
Drown and fall down
そろそろいこか
Let's get going soon
もっと頑張って
Try harder, try even harder...
アガるまでもっと頑張って
...until you get hyped up!
繋がろう ひとり、ふたり、さんにん
Let's connect: one, two, three people
増えたら新鮮 心配ないや
Once they increase, it's fresh—no worries!
All right 任せて Don't mind 波にありのままに
All right, leave it to me, don't mind, just go with the waves
みんなのっかっちゃって
Everyone, hop on board
バーン！
Bang!
アブナイガール 作ろう一手差
Dangerous girl, let's make a difference
半端なら K.O.
If you do it half-heartedly, it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel lightheaded, go ahead.
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready to start the show?
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Whether you cry or laugh, love me still.
ほら Say No
Now, say "No"
低音 響かせろ
Make the bass reverberate
踊 踊 踊
Dance, dance, dance
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Start dancing, start dancing
こねくり回してまわりの目
Stirring things up under everyone's gaze
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Start dancing, start dancing
一歩 二歩 三歩で押し合って
One step, two steps, three steps, pushing each other
くだらないバイバイ Let it go
Nonsensical goodbyes, let it go
どどどどどどどどどどどうなっちゃっても
No matter what happens
どーにかこうにか どうにかこうにかなるでしょう保存
One way or another, we'll make it work somehow
あっぷあんどだうんあてんしょん
Up and down, attention
ドバッと吹き出すような 熱念をトリガーに
With the burning passion blasting out as the trigger!
別に興味ない 特にカンケーない
I don't really care, got nothing to do with me
塞ぎ込んでちゃ損損
Moping around is a total waste!
ラタタタタラ ララララ yeah
Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta-ra, ra-ra-ra-ra, yeah
ほら 澄まして
Look, listen closely
夜光だ
It's phosphorescence
Yeah 泣いていこう
Yeah, let's cry it out
パパパパパパ... パパパパパパ
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa... Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-hearted, it's a K.O.
Uh-oh, wow! Uh-oh, wow!
踊るぜ 踊るぜ 軽くさらっと気取りのノリで
I'll dance, I'll dance, pretending to be light and breezy
Uh-oh, wow! Uh-oh, wow!
言動までお洒落 宵待てパーティだ
Even my behavior is stylish, it's a evening-waiting party
Uh-oh, wow! Uh-oh, wow!
待てぬ拍手をきっと
Surely, the applause that can't wait
Uh-oh, wow! Uh-oh, wow!
実動までお元気で ここらでバイバイ Let's go!
Take care until real action, bye-bye for now, let's go!
This is the end!
Mmm, yeah.
Huzzah!
Is that the last of them? Mmm.
My flame... It grows small due to my nerves.
Oh, I need to shake it off. I can't appear before everyone like this.
Huh?
My phone.
What the frig?!
My karaoke room booking plus... I don't have a lot of time till the showcase!
Okay... Huzzah!
Okay, time to get to karaoke. Come on, Thorn. Okay. Onwards and upwards!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Gomen, alright! Ah, goodbye, parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow!
Sorry, alright! Ah, goodbye, parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow!
Thank you, thank you! Until the next battle, yes, alright.
Here we go. Huzzah!
Alright. Let's go.
[Song: Fallen Angel feat. Aimee B]
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, take me into your skies
There's no place here for me to hide my cries
Night and day, I'm missing you
I know I'm here for the magic
All your stars guiding me through and through
Ooh, why this loneliness feel like forever and ever
I gotta be, I gotta be in your arms, baby
You're so close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but faraway so far I can't touch
I'll hold on
Cuz it's you I love so dearly
When the rain, the storm, and all is done
Caress me with your sweet lullaby...
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, save me in my dreams tonight
Someday, these wings will perish in your sight
Night and day, I call for you
Flashes of moments so tragic
Wandering souls that fall along the way
Tell me you will never leave me forever and ever
I got to be, I got to be in your arms, hear me
You're so close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, I seek for your light
I'll hold on, 'cause for you my heart keeps beating, when the wind, the storm and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Will you be my light?
Will you be my strength?
Promise you won't let me go
I'll never betray
In the end of time
Still my love's gonna be there
You're so close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, so far out of touch
I'll hold on, 'cause for you my love's so deep, when the wind, the storm and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
So close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, I seek for your light
I'll hold on, 'cause for you my heart keeps beating, when the wind, the storm and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Whew!
Hmm... Well...
This song is lovely, but...
for my showcase performance...
should I pick nostalgic songs?
Mmm...
Oh, it's a call.
RyS! My favorite Kohai!
How are you, BB?
Ollie Senpai! Perfect timing.
Actually, I'm having trouble deciding what to sing for my 3D showcase.
Is that all?
Though, I think I speak for everyone when I say...
We'll be happy to hear you sing anything!
As long as you're enjoying yourself, that is.
Y-Yeah, but...
Isn't it standard to pick songs that match your image?
There's like... expectation to be cool, right?
But since this is a special occasion, I was thinking maybe I should show other sides of myself.
Mmm... I see.
Well, you know how powerful you look when you sing?
Yes, yes.
So, I thought, you know, why not try a cute song instead?
Go for that gap-moe appeal, you know what I'm saying?
A cute song... That would be different from usual, which we could, but I'm a bit worried about doing it alone.
Hmm...
Ah! That's it!
What if we invited my brothers-in-arm, Armis, as guests?
That's a great idea!
Seeing cool people singing cute songs?
Oh, the gap-moe will definitely get everybody excited!
Uhh, but it's... still a tad embarrassing.
It'll be fine! Fine!
Come on, try imagining it.
Picture you and Armis singing a cute song together!
Okay...
Me and Armis...
Cute song...
T-T-Together?!
私が私のことを愛して
What's wrong with me
何が悪いの？嫉妬でしょうか？
loving myself? Is it jealousy?
痛いだとか 変わってるとか
Saying I'm cringe or that I'm weird...
届きませんね そのリプライ
Those replies won't reach me!
大好きな洋服
My favorite clothes,
大好きなメイクで
with my favorite makeup,
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いて
curling my usual half-twin tails...
お出かけしよ
Let's go out!
天下持って モテだって
Taking over the world, being popular...
幸せだもん
'Cause I'm happy!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born this way.
チュ！あざとくてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cheeky.
気になっちゃうよね ごめん
It bothers you, doesn't it? Sorry!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for putting so much effort into myself.
チュ！尊くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having so much feminine appeal.
ムカつく？いちゃうよね ざまあ
Are you mad? It's irritating, isn't it? Serves you right!
あなたはあなたのことだけどーぞ
You do you, please.
私に干渉しないでください
Please don't interfere with me.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけれど
They say birds of a feather flock together, but...
届きませんね その陰口
Those backbiting whispers won't reach me!
大好きなピアス
My favorite earrings...
お気に入りのリングで
With my favorite rings...
崩れない前髪クシでといて
Combing my bangs so they won't mess up...
お出かけしよ
Let's go out!
軽い女？ふざけるな
An easy girl? Don't make me laugh!
重すぎるツノ
My horns are way too heavy!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
この時代生きてごめん
Sorry for living in this era.
チュ！目端ててごめん
Mwah! Sorry for standing out.
息しちゃうよね ごめん
You end up sighing, don't you? Sorry!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
自分磨きしててごめん
Sorry for working on myself.
チュ！ぶりっ子でごめん
Mwah! Sorry for acting so innocent.
虜にしちゃってごめん
Sorry for making you fall for me.
ムカつく？いちゃうでしょ ざまあ
Are you mad? Of course you are, serves you right!
趣味の違い 変わり者と
Difference in tastes... even if I'm made fun of...
馬鹿にされても
...as an oddball,
負けたくない 怖くもない
I don't want to lose, and I'm not afraid
あんたらのこと
of people like you!
自分の味方は自分でありたい
I want to be my own greatest ally.
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to treat myself with the utmost care.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I don't want to make myself endure unfair things.
それが 私！
That is... me!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born this way.
チュ！あざとくてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cheeky.
人生楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying my life!
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for putting so much effort into myself.
チュ！尊くてごめん
Mwah! Sorry for being so precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having so much feminine appeal.
ムカつく？いちゃうよね ざまあ
Are you mad? It's irritating, isn't it? Serves you right!
Oh, no.
Maybe, maybe I'm not cut out to be a cute idol like that.
That's not true!
I'm sure everyone wants to see that side of you too, Liz!
Aww, thank you! I feel better about it since you think so, Ollie Senpai!
Makes me happy you think I could be... powerful!
Yeah, yeah! Powerful indeed.
Oh, gosh! Seems like it's the end of my karaoke room booking rehearsal time up here.
Ollie Senpai, thank you so, so much!
All right! Do your best, Liz!
Bye-bye!
I shall. Okay, here we go.
Okay, let's go, let's go. Let's...
Oh, come on!
Here we go. Woohoo!
Hmm... my singing is fine...
But now the physical performance side of bits and bobs is what worries me.
I'm really not too confident.
...about my dancing as I'm a...
...tad rusty.
Oh, what's wrong, Liz?
Zeta Senpai! Well, actually...
I've been worried about my showcase performance...
...as it's getting closer and closer,
and I'm not very confident about my dancing.
Hmm... Is that all? Don't worry, don't worry!
When it comes to dancing, as long as you convey your passion...
...mistakes don't even exist!
Haha, true! But I'm still a bit worried.
Well, in that case, how about this? Come to my jazz club!
If we practice together, I'm sure you'll have more of a spring in your step!
Wait, right now?
Well, that's really nice of you, Zeta Senpai, but you know...
Okay, follow me, Liz!
Oh, we're dancing?
Let's move and groove!
Wait, wait! Zeta!
Wait, what do you mean by move and groove? Whoa, what the... pink!
Yeah!
ギリギリで愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other at the very edge.
めそめそ燃え尽きて夢にして
Stop weeping, burn it all out, and turn it into a dream.
冗談じゃない もっと踊りたい
I'm not joking, I want to dance more.
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore.
I want I want I want 打ち明けてくれ保存
I want, I want, I want... open up your heart to me.
Shalala...
Oh, yeah!
Tick tack
Tick-tack.
危ない目 その仕草
Those dangerous eyes, those gestures...
心見透かされて 欲しくなる​
Seeing right through my heart, making me want you.
既成概念なんて嘘でしょ
Common sense is a lie, isn't it?
はぐらかしてじれったい
Evading me, it's so frustrating.
どうにかなりそう
I feel like I'm going crazy.
落ち着くほどに足りなくなる
The calmer I get, the more I feel lacking.
抱き寄せたら意外なほど
When I hold you close, surprisingly,
寂しい目で睨むから
you glare with lonely eyes,
解き合う回だ
it's time to untangle each other.
ダダダダダダダダダ
Da da da...
ギラギラな夢を見せてよ
Show me a dazzling dream.
全部ばらまいてよ
Scatter it all.
そわそわして
Fidgeting with restlessness,
純情じゃないところも知りたい
I want to know your non-innocent side too.
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore.
I want I want I want 打ち明けてくれ
I want, I want, I want... open up your heart to me.
Shalala...
Oh, yeah!
Your turn. / My turn? Okay.
ドラマなんて飽きたでしょ
You're tired of dramas, aren't you?
二人だけのラスト 書かなくちゃ
A last scene just for the two of us, we have to write it.
運命だなんて戯れ言
Saying it's fate is just nonsense,
演じきればいいんじゃない
isn't it fine if we just play along?
裏腹な言葉で
With contradictory words,
また覚悟を試してくるのに
even though you test my resolve again,
独りきりにさせないでよと
saying "don't leave me all alone,"
悲しみで笑うから
because you smile in sadness,
ずるいよ
it's unfair.
ナナナナナ
Na na na...
ギリギリな恋人たちは
Lovers on the edge...
切ないこの夜も満たせるね
can satisfy even this painful night, right?
見せていいじゃない
It's fine to show it, isn't it?
もっと奥の方
Deeper inside,
震えて弱くなる
shaking and becoming weak.
I want I want I want 打ち明けてくれ
I want, I want, I want... open up your heart to me.
Shalala...
泣かないで それ以上
Don't cry anymore than that,
心を撃ち抜かないで
don't shoot through my heart.
潤ませた瞳に
In your teary eyes,
もう狂わされてしまう
I'm already being driven mad.
官能的な敗北さ
It's a sensual defeat,
もう離せない 離したくない
I can't let go, I don't want to let go.
この指を
These fingers,
these fingers,
この愛を
this love!
ギリギリで信じてほしい
I want you to believe on the edge.
二人なら真実になれる
Together we can become the truth.
告白は最後の機会さ
A confession is the final chance,
もう抱きしめたいよ
I want to hold you tight already.
Yeah!
ギリギリ 愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other on the edge.
嘘も燃え尽くして デリシャスにして
Burn away even the lies and make it delicious.
じゃんじゃんな愛もっと 踊りたい
I want to dance with tons of love.
もう我慢できない
I can't take it anymore!
I want, I want, I want, 打ち明けてくれ
I want, I want, I want, open up your heart to me!
シャラララ... Oh yeah!
Sha-la-la... Oh yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
シャラララ... Oh yeah! Come on! Hey!
Sha-la-la-la... Oh yeah! Come on! Hey!
So, how was it? Once you get into it, it's a good feeling, right?
Dance like nobody's watching. Have fun!
Yes! Somehow, I really gained confidence.
Thank you, Raora-sempai.
Oh, Liz. You always tell others mistakes help them grow and to believe in themselves.
You really need to start taking your own advice.
Listen to your own heart's flame. Let that be your strength.
Yeah, you're right. Sometimes...
...I forget. But thank you for reminding me.
I guess I'm only human.
Here, let me help you take that off.
Hey, but it looks so dapper though, innit? Ooh, so cool!
Wah!
Ouch!
Oops!
With you, Liz, I'm sure your debut will be wonderful. I'm looking forward to it.
As you say, believe in me...
...who believes in thee! Huzzah!
Well, the preparations for the showcase seem to be going smoothly.
So much has happened since we infiltrated Holo. Songs, performances...
...troubles, challenges, and kind words too.
All of them are irreplaceable memories I'll cherish forever.
I want to do my best for my family, my friends, my kingdom...
...and of course, my talented girlies, Justice.
Onwards and upwards!
Flame off.
It has been such a busy day.
Maybe I should rest for a bit.
Yeah, a little... little nap won't hurt anybody.
Raora says I should nap anyways, so it's fine.
一番の宝物 ~Yui final ver.~
Lyrics, Music: 麻枝 准
[Song: My Most Precious Treasure ~Yui final ver.~]
[Lyrics, Music: Jun Maeda]
顔を合わせたら
Whenever we faced each other,
喧嘩してばかり
we did nothing but bicker.
それもいい思い出だった
Even that was a fond memory.
君が教えてくれたんだ もう
Because you were the one who taught me, I'm no longer...
怖くない
...afraid.
どんな不自由でも
No matter what hardships come my way,
幸せは掴める
I can still grasp happiness.
だから
And so...
一人でも行くよ
Even if I am all alone, I will go on,
たとえ辛くても
even if it is painful.
君と見た夢は
The dream I shared with you...
必ず持ってくよ
...I will surely carry it with me.
君とが良かった
I'm so glad it was with you.
あった
I found it...
他の誰でもない
Not with anyone else,
でも目覚めた朝
But when I woke up this morning,
君はいないんだね
you weren't there.
ずっと遊んでる
I felt like we would be playing together forever,
そんな気がしてた
that's what it felt like.
気がしていただけ
But that was only a feeling,
わかってて
even though I already knew.
生まれてきたこと もう後悔はしない
I will never regret being born into this world.
祭りのあとみたい
Like the end of a festival,
寂しいけどそろそろ行こう
it's lonely, but it's time to go.
どこまでも行くよ
I will go on, no matter how far,
ここで知ったこと
holding the things I've learned here close.
幸せという夢
I will make the dream of happiness...
叶えてみせるよ
...come true.
君と離れても
Even if I am parted from you,
どんなに遠くなっても
no matter how far we end up,
新しい朝に
into the new morning,
あたしは生きるよ
I will live on.
一人でも行くよ
I will go on, even all alone,
死にたくなっても
even if I want to die.
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear a voice,
死んではいけないと
telling me that I must not die.
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful,
寂しさに泣いても
even if I cry from loneliness,
心の奥には
deep inside my heart,
温もりを感じるよ
I can still feel your warmth.
巡って流れて
Circling and flowing,
時は移ろいだ
time has moved on.
もう何があったか
I can't even remember...
思い出せないけど
...what happened anymore.
目を閉じてみれば
But when I close my eyes,
誰かの笑い声
I can hear someone laughing.
なぜかそれが今
For some reason, that is now...
一番の宝物
...my most precious treasure.
一人でも行くよ
I will go on, even all alone.
どこまでも行くよ
I will go on, no matter how far.
Mm...
Haaah...
Oh, that dream.
What a beautiful, touching song.
You know what? I should probably add that to my showcase.
My showcase! Oh no!
Flame on!
Oh gosh! I'm going to be late for my showcase! What the fudge?!
All right! My showcase, my showcase, my showcase! All right!
Open the door! Let's go! Come on!
Rosarians!
My Bloodflame Kingdom!
How is the performance thus far?
Let me know what you all think using the hashtag ERB3D!
ERB 3D!
What have you loved most thus far?
Is it this beautiful theater?
The Queen Mother Theater?
Named after my mom. Hi Mom! Hello!
Uh, was it Ollie's appearance?
Flayon and Oga's voiceovers?
Kawaikute Gomen sung with Armis?
Giri Giri with Zea?
Oh gosh! It will make me super-duper happy
hearing your thoughts!
And by the way, I can see you all right now!
Oh my gosh, I see you guys!
I see you at the corner of my eye with a magical, invisible
box made by the Rosarian invisible wizards!
So I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh!
This is crazy!
What do- What do you think about my 3D appearance, huh? Huh?
Uh, let me know in chat right now what poses you would like to see.
Yeah, yeah, let me know!
Yeah, let me know. While you're doing that, I'm going to go get Thorn.
Yeah! It's the one, the only,
Thorn!
Hello, I'm Thorn.
Let's do a quick pose with Thorn, shall we?
Ah...
Hazzah! Hazzah!
All right, let's see what you guys have put.
Um...
Huh? A cat pose?
Oh... All- All right, sure!
Let me just put Thorn over here.
Let's take the jacket off for this one.
Flame off!
Uh... Okay. Uh...
I- I need to become Raora...
Nya. Nya, nya!
Nya. Nya, nya, nya! Nya!
Uh, t-pose?
Okay. That one's easy.
Yes, I shall assert my dominance on you all!
Oh! You know what I want to do?
I want to head-pat you all.
Come here. Head-pat. Head-pat, head-pat.
And hug! Hug! We must do this, we must hug!
Hug, hug!
Hug! One more!
We got her, we got her.
Um, let's see...
What else do you want? Victory pose?
Like this?
Yes, I am victorious! For I am...
...the Queen of the Bloodflame Kingdom!
Yeah.
I love you all very much, too. I'm so happy you're all here.
Oh gosh!
Absolute cinema, yes!
Okay.
Oh, a twirl? Okay, we'll do a twirl.
All right.
Yes.
A twirl...
Wow!
Is that okay? A twirl.
Jazz hands.
A spin? Spin, twin!
Oh gosh. A curtsy? Oh, that's a good one.
Like this... A curtsy.
And a bow.
Cute? Hey, you mean, you mean powerful, right?
Powerful! Yes, yes, yes, powerful!
I know you guys also like my shocked face.
So let me just think of something really shocking.
Um...
What the frig!
What the frig? Time is nearly up for poses!
I guess it's time for the next song.
Would you like to hear another song?
Yes, sure you do!
All right, just wait one moment. I need some bits and bobs for this one.
All right.
Some bits and the bobs and the bobs and the bits.
Pa-ba-da-pa-da.
All right.
Here we go. Here's the bits and the bobs.
I have a stand.
It's my mic! Look at that!
And I have a guitar.
Ha! I'm so kakkoii!
Ha! I'm so cool!
All right.
Uh, let's go with a cute... I mean, a powerful song next.
Please listen to...
私の恋はホッチキス
My Love is a Stapler
The next song is My Love is a Stapler.
Let's go!
なんてなんだろう 気気になる理由は
What could it be, the reason I'm curious...
君への この想い
...is these feelings for you.
便箋に書いてみるよ
I will try writing them in a letter.
もしかして 気まぐれかもしれない
Could it be that it's just a whim?
それなのに 枚数だけ増えていくよ
But despite that, the number of sheets keeps growing.
好きの確率 割り出す
To calculate the probability of love,
計算式あればいいのに
if only there was a formula...
キラキラ光る願い事も
Even shining, glittering wishes
ぐちゃぐちゃへたる悩み事も
and messy, exhausted worries...
そうだ ホッチキスでとじちゃおう
That's right, let's staple them together!
とじちゃおう！
Let's staple them!
はじめの一歩だけは軽いノリで
Taking only the first step with a light attitude,
知らないうちに熱くなって
before I know it, I've grown passionate.
もう針がなかったら通らない
If there are no staples left, it won't work,
また明日
see you tomorrow!
どうしようかな
What should I do?
読み返してみるの 恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing to read it over,
あれこれと 便箋に
even though I wrote all sorts of things...
書いたくせに
...on the letter sheets.
気持ちごと ゴミ箱行きじゃなんだか
If I throw my feelings into the trash can,
この胸が切ないから
my chest would ache so much.
持っていようかな
Maybe I'll keep them with me...
今の気持ちを表す 辞書にもない
...to express my current feelings that aren't even in the dictionary.
...ない
...even...
言葉
for words...
探すよ
I will search.
One, two, three!
ワクワクしちゃう計画とか
Exciting plans or...
グダグダすぎる展開とか
totally messy developments...
ぜんぶホッチキスで
Let's staple them all and...
とじちゃおう
bind them together!
今日のできごと 思い出して
Remembering today's events,
いつも心が キュンとなって
my heart always skips a beat.
もう針がないから
Now that there are no staples left,
買わなくちゃ
I have to buy some.
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow!
キラキラひかる願い事も
Sparkling wishes and...
グチャグチャへたる悩み事も
messy, depressing worries...
そーだホッチキスで
That's right, with a stapler,
とじちゃおう
let's bind them together!
はじまりだけは 軽いノリで
It only started as something casual,
しらないうちに あつくなって...
but before I knew it, it became passionate.
もう針がなんだか
Somehow, the staples...
通らない
won't go through anymore.
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow!
And that was "My Love is a Stapler"!
How was it? Did you like my guitar playing?
Well, you guys know this,
but...
I'm actually...
a professional air guitarist!
I know, I know!
Surprise, shocker!
Professional air guitarist here.
Look out!
Anyhoo...
Now it's time for an announcement!
Everyone,
let's call...
for our favorite four-legged friend...
Bobby!
Three, two, one...
Come here, Bobby. You're such a good boy.
He's a good boy!
Yeah! Show yourself to the camera.
Do a little twirl or something, yeah.
Oh, you're so cute!
Wait a minute... What the freak?
Bobby!
Bobby...
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Oh, big hug!
He's... he's such a...
little cheeky guy,
little cheeky guy!
Oh, golly!
Well,
as you can see on Bobby's head,
the announcement is...
Merchandise!
Oh my goodness, we have this!
Ta-da!
Wow, a paper knife letter opener...
inspired by my sword, Thorn!
A set product that includes an acrylic stand...
where you can plop your mini Thorn into.
It looks real cool on your desk,
and you'll get all the maidens.
I should know, a lot of them have visited
my dressing room to see the prototype.
And that's no lie! It's pretty awesome.
And also, the sale dates
will be after
the Justice collaboration stream.
So, once that's all done and dusted,
it will be out there on the shop!
And that concludes the merchandise.
Thank you, Bobby!
Everybody thank Bobby.
Thank you so much!
You're such a good boy, you're such a good boy, yes you are!
All right,
back to the Duke and the Queen Mother you go.
Gosh...
I honestly can't believe it. Time has...
flown,
and...
it's already time for our last, final, seventh song.
Seven!
This has been quite the journey and a half.
So before I end, I just want to...
thank everyone: the cast...
our wonderful guests, the crew, managers...
the director. Thank you so much.
Thank you for your hard work, thank you so much.
And of course, my friends, my family, my beautiful Kingdom...
Thanks for supporting me so much.
I wouldn't be standing here right now.
Not only do I get to fight for justice...
but, um...
with my wonderful girlies, Raora, Gigi...
And Gigi, and Cecilia...
but I also get to do what I love,
so thank you so much.
I get to give the gift of smiles...
...and strength through the art of performance and singing!
I hope I can do this forever,
and we can keep spreading smiles...
...throughout the realms together.
That would make me so happy!
Anyway, before the allergies hit me too much...
Oh, let me just move my stand.
Allergies, guys, the allergies!
I can't stand this stand!
It must get out of the way.
Don't mind me!
All right... Wait a minute.
Before I do my last tune,
we gotta bring back my beautiful backing dancers, right?
Come on, flame on!
Ah, and they're back.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? Yes, yes, yes!
And now, for our final song,
please listen to: Hero too!
Hands up!
I want to be an idol and a hero for all of you too! Let's go!
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
What am I to be?
What is my calling?
I gave up giving up,
I'm ready to go.
Future's left unseen,
it all depends on me.
Put it on the line
to follow my dream, yeah!
Tried, all my life I've tried...
...to find
something that makes me hold on...
...and never let go,
Oh!
Hero too,
I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too,
strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes
stand up for what they believe.
So wait and see,
Yeah!
so wait and see!
What do they think of me?
Who do they think I'll be?
I could not care less,
I don't wanna know.
Am I doing right?
Am I satisfied?
I wanna live my life
like it's meant to be, yeah!
Tried, all my life I've tried...
...to find
something that makes me hold on...
...and never let go,
Oh!
Hero too,
I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too,
strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes
stand up for what they believe.
So wait and see!
People will judge
for no reason at all.
And they might try to drag
your dreams down,
don't listen!
They may look down on me
and count me out,
I'm going my own way.
They may look down on me
and count me out,
I'm a hero
and I've got news!
Hero too,
I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too,
strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes
stand up for what they believe.
Hero too,
I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too,
strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes
stand up for what they believe, so wait and see!
I have met so many heroes in my life,
they gave me the strength and courage to survive,
gave me the power to smile every day,
now it's my turn
to be the one to make you smile!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
To make you smile!
Yeah!
Woo!
Phew!
Parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you tomorrow!
Make sure to eat good noms.
もぐもぐ。
Munch, munch.
Hydrate,
みずみず、
gulp, gulp,
and get good sleeps,
ねるねる。
snooze, snooze.
As we want our Bloodflame Kingdom to be happy and strong!
大きくなれ！
Grow big!
Let's try our best together.
これからも一緒に頑張ろう！
Let's keep doing our best together from now on!
Onwards!
And upwards!
And don't forget...
...that my voice is your strength.
ちゅっちゅ。
Kiss, kiss.
Cheer for everyone as loud as you can, Rosarians!
Hosanna!
QUEEN MOTHER ELIZABETH'S 3D SHOWCASE!
Dear Rosarians, my beautiful Sparks of Joy
The smiles and happiness I got
performing for you all
from performing for you all,
I'll cherish and forever appreciate
Thank you for making my wishes come true
BIG HUGS my Bloodflame Kingdom - Liz